Sau vat' in warm what's step number one
boot
turn off mobile phones
[music]
lenses my father was not a breakthrough in
time began to achieve because   The
man himself said, "These are the initiatives to
attach sounds to you,
more discs, disappointment and anger, and
they will start growling like this, what have
you become, fugue, his litinen game,
please don't forget that you are
meditating in a group, conservatives,
try to be attentive
to each other, sofa in pain, these are also
cleavers,
suffering and pain, several Tasmania,
Raja Yoga on the Internet, and your new words
for yoga in Chinese, Mitya, all so
free, mutual suffering, and so
endure it, illuminate prayers, you
teach meditation, and cattle, water,
monster, well, familiar with the traditional
warm-up, observed, and on veganism, and
we did it this morning in a
relaxed manner, traditional
warm-up, and always meditation, and is it really worth it for
you to study this one, and figures,
trainer, pray, and mother from the channel, we watch
them, if you do meditation, which
will be my sandwich for 20 minutes, it would be good for you
to make a face, warm-up, so
if you teach a group of people and drink
scans, team magic meditation will
last more than 20 years, does  Warm up with
it, you can cover warm up if you
want.
My goal is to warm up most like I've always, just like
before you install a
lock, warm up your feet. Entina China,
Osman, it will come out, yes, just a
month of balance. We taught a
balance course, files of parts, talents, and
for fun, we did balancing. It was great for
all the students. They
brought modeling lessons.
If you're not Flynn, ballet steps are now
balancing. But in order to
do this, you need to warm up. The cashier told
him half an hour, otherwise it will be the same. The same
with meditation.
Now you're Hannigan. Today, my date,
we'll go through the standard map. Go home.
Pray for where the ocean will warm you up.
Tell me, we'll bend our claws on the balance.
7 recipes are assigned. I like it.
I warmed up the first one. These are the bad seeds we
've sown over the last
few. Meat here, which can
interfere with our meditation. This is called
for masks and to compete. An injection of
powerful, my good forces strives for
our consciousness before we begin. Our consciousness strives for quite a lot,
and therefore, warming up with oil is ready
for meditative muscles before meditation.  and the
sab segments, how this ends, the volume, that
is, clean out fresh bad seeds
that can affect your consciousness,
from the old ones from the dye, collect new
good seeds that will help a more
powerful meditation. Therefore, if you do
37 warm-ups,
the distance will be better because,
as we did yesterday, the Chilean meditation also
happens in the test, so if we
very, very much and ours and the quick planting of
good seeds right before the
creator's meditation, it will go better. So,
let's start with your processor,
fearing
micro with warm-up requires
heavy otitis powerful karmic objects.
The most powerful karmic object is this
important to decide if I and as
you teach serially and you may want
atheists, you will steal than him to
the heart of what can be on and
whether that is, maybe the student will become
what to feel in such a way that you
will become their heart weak. Islam and
young in many cases itself the people
bridge stage, we will teach many
people who do not yet know you or they
already have another heart, this is in parts of the
Tethys monastery. I was 12 different teachers at the
time.  English courses gish but only
one or two of them we shoot with my
heart lamas
you are not ast and stylists big-bags us actor
so when you ask very your no one will
give and you begin they will do it
imagine your teacher
so you can go roach 16
use the teacher with whom they
feel not much closeness
this can be so maybe not you will
remain when you begin sargent
understand these with these ribbons
I would say that imagine behind my
your teacher but how
close a connection it may not be I can
violent someone in your life until now
you met him and radio to the bodies who
taught you
to maybe your mom and dad your
escape or where teachers
and external exact great teachers even
if you did not have very good
relationships with them in the past or
now the relationship is strained
mom carried you for 9 months from such
fractions risked her life to
revive and start with even if he was not an
excellent father I supported the family
and as a rule correctly and hard
I worked him in difficult days so that you
This is your first great
teacher with Actin, it's always appropriate to use them for a
while, Sandra, past the warm-up, imagine
your father or mother, imagine
that she is in the room,
your meditation, and together with them, you can
do with shares because they are heavy
karmic, Angelos, powerful, I also
like to list other teachers that
children might have had, a school
teacher when you were young, songs, or
your teachers in college, some special
teachers,
I know, for example, that I had
five very special ones with an
actor, valuable teachers, and 13 can be
done, you can change somersaults painfully
every day, you can use different
steam, or if you feel a very close
connection
with one teacher,
your heart teacher, then you can
do this, a gram with them, or at least a
larger amount of money, not
just to diversify meditation,
diversity, meditation is very good,
sometimes I like to tell people that
obviously you have many different teachers in your life
and teachers who taught you
your profession, one example, if a hacker
hovers, you can also become an
investment manager and
become one, or you sell cars and
this skill, and learn from someone, for example,
in the diamond business
It's a very long learning process.
If you make a mistake, Azamora can
lose a lot of money. Therefore, there were
many teachers who taught
this skill. They weren't obligated to
teach it, but they were very
kind and didn't
press. They spent almost 10 years of
work
teaching me and the damage inflicted by the Reds on
business. I don't assume that you
had a similar person in your life. Goods in Iraq.
In general, you have these
tides of teamwork for this skill.
Some like to ask a
teacher to be present for the maintenance of someone who has already died. Some
historical teachers, which
maybe you've never noticed. Maybe
many Westerners like to do
this with Jesus. If you grew up,
you grew up, you went into the Muslim tradition.
This could be about the growth of the Prophet Muhammad. It
depends on who you feel a
great affinity with. Some teachers from
the past were great.
We will say that these were most likely
booths. They can't draw you. They can
read your mind.
As you begin your
meditation, it is appropriate to invite them into the
room as heavy karmic objects. A
powerful end time so that in an hour,
jar  The final choice,
by the way, and your family can also be
aspasia,
and while our husbands and your wife are pouring in, they follow the
diamond remote control, and all parents know
that children in Linz are wonderful teachers. I don't
know, I had students who
felt like you were really your
pet, for example, a dog or a
cat. I didn't feel that these doctors and
animals were taught as if this was also
normal. If you want to do it yourself, I
understood. I'm filming. Finally, the last choice. You
want them, maybe a teacher you have
n't met yet. Maybe in this life
above, they haven't found their heartfelt
teacher, and in the bank, but you would like to. Do you
think you would find one? You're planting the
fact that you share your wisdom with
other people who want to hear about it. We'll hear as
you do it. In
fact, Sarzhan, you can invite a
teacher who isn't worth joking about.
Your ideal future teacher. You
can imagine how they might
look in the dirt, or how whose
face you might act. In this case, according to
tradition, someone through whom you make a
sadzha should be very happy that you
invited him into this room with something of a
different type. Tradition imagines
closed eyes, and we are
watching me.  With great love and sympathy, and they are
very proud of you. You are the spotlights that you
decided to meditate today in the house and
promises to meditate regularly.
They are very happy that you invited them to
communities to tighten and when you serve
weed to your students, I
play with a very important thing to encourage these
so that they do not think
stories about the teacher and who sits
doubts really think about him as a
picture like the rest. We do not
meditate with a piece of paper with a
metal stage, you meditate with a
real living person. This did not
act. 37. It seems very useful to me.
This is a tradition to imagine how their
chest rises, they fall in every
breath. Athens when not entering the
room, you can feel a certain
warmth. We do not feel how the wind
blows you. They will not appear. They do not go around
you. You feel how it shifts. They
sit opposite you. Buddhism. The restaurant is
very good. Thank you
with the mayor. Other. What special smell could
be the smell of some kind of incense. Anakin,
their scroll, could be the smell of the ocean. They
have a special smell that their
bodies emit from good deeds and din. And people
who do not eat meat for a long time
also have some sweet smell.
Smell, imagine that your teacher
smells special and they look
at you with very happy eyes and you
invited them to sit, this is mom, become
him with you. I like to imagine
stein sitting table, your knees
practically touching, they will be an
important karmic object for your
sak-chan ga, that is, mom and saints and 1
warm-up is to greet through the
sign,
respected, with us, you can imagine
what to do and spatial and
acted and you can imagine that you
hold your hands in front of the set has a more acute topic
Helen Dudy for
the tradition of prostration, worship in
Buddhism
Aksenova came from the reaction of a person
who just saw emptiness had
direct perception of a bush, I wonder what this is the
first time you see Buddha
and she is metse and did not score 100
direct perception for this was and the person
who saw let the question immediately
make complete
they will not prostration automatically
even if no one has ever taught them, they have
never seen how this is done for
the driver, therefore, when we meet
our teacher, after all, we appear to him, we are
preserved for the
reason that we do, I bow
So you're saved, you're not talking about what else
you respect, that person has something powerful, the
moment he just things are very special
for you, so mentally, not
before, like Zonya, you know, and
meditate, you just need to think about what
you admire in this person, words
or different languages ​​at once and words, as we
say, admiration for Olga Seymour,
it's the same necks, so measure signs
cannot be dispensed with. I look at my teacher, I
take Fuqua, we have some wonderful
qualities and they are ones that I admire
if you think about it, dateline, this is the
reason why you asked them to
teach you risk because you want
ordinary with these qualities, ideally, you
want very Tevs Kevin, the teacher doesn't
just give you information, you
want whiskey, a minivan, the teacher gives you an
example, these cops, simple accounts,
instantly bow down, there's a
warm-up for meditation, sambuca, us,
and then they some wonderful boys,
this teacher helped, tried, including, I
can sometimes say that he gets
great joy from helping the
elderly and sick people or spends a
lot  Part of the day and night, or exactly for
this,
so here I would like to pause.
These are the things that are good for you to teach,
teach time, what to collect, and powerful
seeds during meditation. When it begins, I
would like to ask you to
invite your teacher, please
go into the room, invert together with, so as to
do mentally and worship,
think of one quality that you
decide on for your teacher, samber, when you
think of some quality, comics with
your teacher and a
link to collect powerful karmic ones, it
will make your situation much more powerful in 5-10 minutes,
so volare, therefore, the quality of your
visits in this productive tradition and
it depends on, as far as I know, you
can imagine the good
quality of your teacher and something they will
do for you, and to living examples,
cook, or those qualities that you would
like to teach, so let's pronounce
and the teacher of
any teacher who is closer to you on May 5th,
whom you admire something, some of
his qualities, and so on, and here is
for export, sak-chan, the next part,
our native ninka with janka,
is to make an offering to this teacher,
clarity,
this is at the same time  And gratitude and a request, a
request, one of the Utah camera, if a
parent, as you
become teachers of families in Africa, people
will begin to offer you an offering of VPN
in April, maybe a pen, maybe
it will be a house, and the rest
will begin to understand things more fantasy, an
offering to the head of the person receiving the
offering, they only flowed their givers,
give when you are just starting to
teach, you are starting a teacher in India,
you really like these things that
people looked at, for example, someone
gives you a tank, a
sweater, a book, or a pen, volumes,
people give you money, offer an Audi and
the risk of Riga, a state or a car or a
house, something significant and swelling of the axis oy
questionnaire as a young teacher ate
you are pleased and
with females you feel some
pride and goodness less than 5 that people give
attention to nage does not give you alms, I would
like to say a couple of things about these, I will get
first,
short-lived, not very important, the mystery of
roosters, this kingdom, people who give the
biggest,
they expect something else from you, something
more than just teaching, do not want your
attention, maybe even your sympathy,
decades of mini  There can be many
reasons why people give alms.
Often, people who give the largest
offerings want something from you. This
has nothing to do with the teachings of
Evanescence. Even if these
offerings are sincere, they
disappear, and you use them, or you
lose a lot.
John Ikon, other experienced teachers,
cannot say that giving for a long time is
not very important. This will be money, this is
good, it does not tick, and it is
intelligent to give gifts and
accept and use them if
appropriate. But as you
mature, you understand that the
real style of beading and receiving from
our students is seeing how they become
happier and happier. See how their
situation improves. Their
yoga improves health, especially
seeing how their consciousness improves. Their
relationships are characterized by patience, and death is virtue.
As you develop, as we
read the tent,
well, all the treatments of time
will switch from physical [likely referring to] padar India
to sex with you. 10 very joy from the success of
your hotel in a day.  The peak is one
joy for your serious students behind the inverter
who become good
people in the process of charging NTS 10 according to the
tradition of feel and we offer the
forest began and we visualize a new
car or a new house and office
you offer and visible I am not your
progress your improvements your fr activism
I am sick Erdely their this year than
last one tea I tried I have
not yet succeeded I still have many
shortcomings daily but he did in
general work hard that Bishtov is a
better person I offer you May
lubrication my small successes the most cinema
so create relationships through the network in the
background of me too incredible seeds of that
meditation but I will move in 10
minutes
now we are making a garden of negativity
make offerings to this teacher Uncle
Sam this couple
car and there is where wearing Samantha
undermining you imagine the whole sky
filled with roses or lotus flowers
Aizen all five happy cars and faith
if Ostapenko has the best coffee
you drank this year
yourself some chapters you can do with
him stages but the top relationships which they will
really enjoy  And the tone in relation to
which you will create ideal, as it is
already impossible to see the improvement of students,
you see their happiness.
Yandex ports covered the next stage.
Sarzhan says, in the next part, X-ray warm-
ups for meditation, Yant
retina 15. As a teacher, a
TV presenter of an organization, you must
evaluate how much time you have. Give
the angle of light with an active. If you have
time for the whole juice, Jan will feel like dying as
you teach. Meditation is
sensitive in relation to the fact that
people's attention to this and the initial quickly
dissipates within half an hour. Their hand
and decline and time every minute. Dio and
memory to him during meditation and
save the intro, which is especially difficult in the
era of the Internet and mobile phones. It is
very difficult for people to focus; they
quickly get tired during meditation, so you
need to move towards meditation
quickly enough. Stenosis is too slow, where
otherwise you will lose people's attention. Those
who live with a mobile phone
cannot focus for more than
a few minutes, so be careful
not to take up all the time like Janga,
then you will not have time left for the
meditation itself. While we are doing
two big things today, our teacher  This is a
good seed we admired than before them,
this mental worship and then we,
you are pure with a small one, make the shores of the real
attitude of the small ones above, they are our enemies
and because if you, like me, drink it
and when you report on your
improvements through your teacher during
almsgiving, automatically begin to think
about all those things that you are not deprived of. The
10th mistake you made when I
do from under the night to my teacher,
I can sincerely say that I made
only small improvements, this
immediately contain make me realize all
these mistakes that I made,
go continue to do, slept with tactics from the
Ansa plant, the
next part of the list of Django to me suck
at Jong, they admitted
he is very, very honest about the method, I don’t
hide anything, I’m not ready, this is all with you, it’s
not as difficult as telling the teacher
directly everything that you did bad
during meditation
with who drove away Girin, we can get into the
habit of being absolutely honest with our
teachers,
think about all those mistakes
that are committed, continue with all the
bad habits that  last for years
or even decades. Be honest with
your teacher. You'll say, "
I'm so sorry." If I were stronger,
diabetics
could stop all these things. But do
n't be honest about your good habits yet. Aha, blush,
and your religion. A negative
attitude. And so, measuring them by
admitting your mistakes or making anyone in
your environment crazy. A
very powerful way to
stop these bad seeds.
Next, form with an actor. The next element
means forests, southerner, this is what we
call coffee meditation in Odessa,
pumpkin, content ID. Otherwise, we'll tell you everything. He's
good at what you've done. Small
improvements. Also, you can think about the
wonderful things
other people do and fly in the form and offer
them to your teacher. There's everything for me on my
website. 2 warm-ups with sak dzhankoy, which
is an attitude. The highest thing about
attitude is your practice. 2 and 4. 4
should also be joyful about your
small improvements. Small successes
intersect when we think about this one
small progress,
which is ideal. I suggest wars to
foreigners. Steps, and when I get to step
4, I suggest  that the ride is chasing, but for
me these two steps are not very different from
each other.
Italy and what we noticed here is that I and a
strong 30 thousand people every year are a
very interesting thing and removing the father-in-law is the
most difficult step for almost everyone
we meet.
Laricheva people have a lot of difficulties in
the world
to admit you will do something
right. We all love to brag,
or praise ourselves
weakly, but we have a problem. At that moment,
when is such a time to
truly love ourselves deeply and admire what
we do, brother, and
as a rule, we focus more on the
mistakes we make with
activity, so during this step,
sadja number 4,
try your best to think about how
lucky you are to
give money without knowing all these
z  The wonderful things in your life are that
you are here meditating,
inside you are inside, very
holy, very powerful, the type of line itself,
transmission from the tank itself, about you, also
fatin and the rest, such is the fat now,
hope for as much as is lucky of
all the hundreds of millions of people in this world,
especially for the boxing great cleaning,
tested guards
when it doesn’t say that I am in this
room, it’s better to acquire no
one mounts like I do when not
constantly comparing myself with other
people,
we do and persistent keys,
private lessons, and Andre said yesterday that
maybe you will watch
other people, Vladik, compare yourself with
others, but he definitely does it during the
headstand, know only because
you can injure your neck, give an account of yours,
my main thing is that I did yoga yesterday, it
wasn’t easy, but I did it, not pride,
that I did my meditation, have the appearance of doing a
retreat at the Diamond Harry Center,
diamonds, I make a lot of mistakes,
many of them very old mistakes, we
really try, I try,
I’m here now, is this very powerful seeds
for good meditation that will be
through  10 minutes installer here inside
you like to change a little
yourself there this some days you
can think about those ethyl good
things that other people do
for example the topic no matter how hard worked
jigme has been helping for many years you can
rejoice John Wick they are very lucky
and that so many with such dedication of children
give themselves to the process of Maria bitters
teach could give so much hope to
people in Russian-speaking countries we can
experience joy for the seeds of other
people
as teachers of meditation
elders adopted will begin to burn these steps
closer to the end
people then again to this attention to
you the door quickly gets lost during
half an hour of vindication closer to the end they are
much more very tired
he is looking for about sucks on guy we are almost
finished by the way as a teacher and 33 is a very
good strategy 3 in Moscow does not tell
his students that we are almost
finished very many yoga teachers
say let's hold this pose for another second 2 seconds
and then they hold
you in this benefit for another minute
very good sedative tell you
about almost finishing soon a break
we only need one or two more allowed the
next element and then warm-up
10 ticks of city residents, ask
your teacher to continue teaching you,
never stop teaching me, she
will heal
my, no one likes to share my
own life experiences and my
students, and those people who
hurt me in my life
taught me more than those people who
were kind to me,
especially when you have problems, difficulties from
someone else, you deepen your
understanding of your life and understanding of
emptiness and service is my style, and I
like to share with my students, that
is, you ask for teaching
openly from the world, then next week you
can get many new problems that you asked to get
out,
asked for teachings,
when you ask for teachings, these are not always
teachings in this format, not always teachings with
books or dances or the style of the
greatest teachers, these are the people who
call problems in your life, people
who do not reward, who demand
time from you,
like drawing hooks, people who
criticize you, so be careful,
long backs,
not during this warm-up, when you
ask for teachings, and we must consciously
remember, say all the greatest teachings
are the greatest challenges and difficulties, and
Be grateful to those people who
teach you this way.
Again, you can speed up
these stages as your students get tired. The
last step we will
take today, after which we will take a break. I was looking for
when we ask our teacher to stay
in our life. It is very difficult to
sow enough good,
strong anti-to meet your
teacher. Probably many then
accumulated. Sasha, I
have a friend who calls his
previous life and John says on Joe, it was
not me who created this teacher. My previous
life worked for me more intensely
than I myself. It is this heavenly life that
created this wonderful teacher. If
any, my task is to create
enough good seeds so that the teacher does
not leave me or does not die or we are
somehow separated. Life is a
man eating with Artem, so the last
step, Jan,
we ask our teacher, please
stay in my life. This is a license. This
request if she sincerely sees them
and creates enough strength to leave
them with you. You are mine. There is nothing sadder
in the world when a father or mother loses their
child. If you talk to them, they
will tell you that I hope that I die
sooner. There is nothing more.  It's painful to
hope it's 3 than for a father or mother
to lose their child on ti1 saint,
but losing your teacher is still
much harder.
The goals are therefore we want to sincerely
ask them to stay.
Now we are doing such
meditation and here we will just take a
break. You can open your eyes and
stretch.
Auto.
I will announce the official. It is known to
sign after the questions. Paretto. Does
anyone have questions or bar rollers? Would
anyone like to keep everyone from
going to the toilet? Well, okay, I don't feel
any guilt.
Ask a question. I don't have a question. I just
wanted everyone to support you. Follow up from
going to the toilet. No, actually, there is a
question. It's difficult during practice.
Visualization. I begin. I feel
great anxiety. This is mental
gymnastics.
When I am very relaxed, it is much
easier. But in the morning, it is
very difficult to do these visualizations.
If I am like this, and you can do it for now, then
I have two suggestions for you. A
computer. They both come from the scriptures. And
the guests are honey-bearing. 1 is the most important thing for me,
and on a file. 150 years old, it is very
pleasant to give hints on the interests of
fairy tales. To bite a person is more important
and often they feel,
and we seem to  I would juggle, yes, that's
why I definitely need to
pull back the creature, absolutely Washington, and
truly, mothers, run with a branch, shape,
smoothly, you can do it together, it's not a pain,
ring, hold the dough, that's how the fire is
behind, I will continue to do it through,
also, some books on the nation say
that just imagine the outlines of it,
some
dough and give my couple never so much
more correctly, they can put their
toes and then you can't
focus on anything else, Hitler,
feel the joy about them being
awarded to the Levins,
that they are finally in the room, that they are in the room,
this is the main thing,
this is important, cola, apparently, not colors and shape,
no idea yet, what kind of locks for Pepe
are in the room, thank you, Kesha, when I
meditate for more than 30 or 40 minutes, I
feel tension between my eyebrows, I don't
know what to do with it, good teaching
from you, yesterday was the first time for me
when you talk about how when we
close our eyes, you said that you can hold your
eyes, keep your
eye level slightly above the
horizon, it helps me, a beautiful
large garden, and I started doing this, I talk about this and
say I want to do it again  Repeat keepup
if I teach read plays back eyes
Vologda good and Dave
and when at school you met then
guys will come beautiful outfits so edit
thrilled from the famous want just once
focus and I can only give those
tips skopich when this
second design of the book design from France
became
like it is very distracting therefore and not in the
world crack in meditation
try to keep very class in
simple all this is just
monochromatic know how when I go on retreat
is a serious person who does
retreats twice a year and companies for a
month now I often and the file we go
depending on what you can
afford without getting fired from
work well I'll fight
and arteries that I am enough to be
good goes by the author we will violate look for
houses for whether club nargile is very
bad zones
they are very good people from retreat at
home or in your apartment there are too
many stories these white department ideally it
was good on the internet somewhere in nature
get out to
some quiet place and in the spring throw
pumpkin one dacha tried  Make noise now
when gifts are too much, visit my review of
this I would do when the lark is
cooking rice right there, I put away all the magazines and books,
everything where there is a scripture, where the
hellish miner is, remove it, but we didn't know how to do it from
mine, you remember when I meditate, I'm generally a
lover of books and fast food, so when I
see a book in the store, I look at a magazine, a very
nice one, and
our three-year-old retreat on the exhale, and
while we were fighting, we decided to do
nothing except a prayer book,
but in general, how and then we started
reading cereal boxes ourselves, no matter how many people were
arrested for these, each cereal, in that at least something, with a
mast, sitting down and places, this is
my application to you, still keep your eyes slightly
open, try to keep the probe lower
on the boil, but still don't lower it, no
further, the saddle is doing the eyes, this is
normal, how to open it, still
look down, the shadows, let your
chin drop to release the gaze,
who with ordinary heads tyute launch into
this, keep your chin at level, become a
guarantor, and so all these, you will  You're a
statue,
maybe the same thing, right now we have an operator, but
regarding the tension, here I am and no
one is investigating. I
feel tension in my chest or my
first ones. What's wrong with Joe, who do
redirects at home, downsell mobile, squirrels,
don't let go of the deal, what could
happen? No, you have to do something. It will get
worse. We have standards,
it's about us, don't cry, it's a blockage
there. Fiscal thinks that she herself will
do something anyway. And regarding this, this
speaks of some kind of fermentation growth,
as a rule, the simplest solution is not the most
correct analysis. One small
smile. Mona Lisa Ann Grigorov and mine.
Muscles. We're going to
France in May and they'll want to see the Mona
Lisa in the Louvre,
and minus on the graph. Old man, I don't know. I'm
not desperate, but her smile is cool. It
seems to me that you're an
artist. While this smile
relaxes me, eat until the end, and my face
tenses. Overall, it's all the same. Smart cubes.
Usually, I liked it here. She's behind my
spine, so there might be
some discomfort. That's my backlog. There's
more risk. Doors for this.  Maybe they made it in time.
The day is wonderful, and it's a traditional
traction. And if you have a taller Anderson, the
guy tensed up. Focus on the war.
Even a
powerful hearth doesn't mean anything. Mom, something.
When you should focus on
your kidney skills, the tubercle
that you're talking about right now is closed. Sandel's
baroque step is behind the goddess and at
navel level, but she's behind the spine. I
saw this. If you visualize, there are no
tits,
even your teachers don't set anything in front of
you. Insert them for your benefit.
Tomorrow, these are different scenes for you, side from
these two areas, you definitely
can't wait for
them to help us somehow, of course, as a
neighbor, you will have to, we have no weapons,
you will generally stop meditating on
people who caused damage from these
diagrams and they wrote it off for a week, they
still have problems, they went to someone's
teacher, which
they will teach incorrectly even 50 years later, Rublev,
so don't do it, just...
This is serious, Olyk Andy, barter, so you
think there's no need to wait for
your floor to be destroyed. This is something you need to
work on right away. Lower it back, even
visualization, even a llama,
this will help you. It will help. Try
good
long-term details. That when you
eat, serious illnesses sang wars, and also
that heavy engine drivers, yours in our
culture, it will be put oil on top.
Oil really helps in lowering it. Is it
true there's a thousand abusive things there that they're
very fat.
Oyama shook herself with large stones.
Oil is something in which the relics are often sought with oil. I
can also let's make a
toilet. Memas, how about you, and then we'll start. Lam
Rim,
that is, a comeback at nine o'clock.
You were looking for jumping on the windows, please
go back to nine o'clock. Everyone.